{
    "questions": [
    {
    "question" : "In the U.S., if it's not Daylight Saving Time, it's what?",
    "content" : [
        "Borrowed time",
        "Overtime",
        "Standard time",
        "Party time"
    ],
    "correct" : 2
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which part of the body are you most likely to \"stub\"?",
        "content" : [
            "Toe",
            "Knee",
            "Elbow",
            "Brain"
        ],
        "correct" : 0
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which country is largest by area?",
        "content" : [
            "UK",
            "USA",
            "Russia",
            "China"
        ],
        "correct" : 2
    },
    {
        "question" : "What does the \"F\" stand for in FBI?",
        "content" : [
            "Foreign",
            "Federal",
            "Flappy",
            "Face"
        ],
        "correct" : 1
    },
    {
        "question" : "An albino gorilla usually has what color fur?",
        "content" : [
            "Brown",
            "Black",
            "White",
            "Golden"
        ],
        "correct" : 2
    },
    {
        "question" : "When you enter a situation without a definite plan of action, you are said to be \"playing it by\" what?",
        "content" : [
            "Fingertips",
            "Ear",
            "Nose",
            "Mouth"
        ],
        "correct" : 1
    },
    {
        "question" : "What is commonly known as the \"Emerald City\" in the United States?",
        "content" : [
            "Palos Verdes, CA",
            "Seattle, WA",
            "New York, NY",
            "Dallas, TX"
        ],
        "correct" : 1
    },
    {
        "question" : "What is the national emblem of Canada?",
        "content" : [
            "Maple Leaf",
            "Brown Bear",
            "Maple Syrup",
            "Waffle"
        ],
        "correct" : 0
    },
    {
        "question" : "What is the name of the largest freshwater lake in the world?",
        "content" : [
            "Lake Union",
            "Lake Superior",
            "Lake Largest",
            "Lake Goodwin"
        ],
        "correct" : 0
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which of the following consumer goods is the Gerber Products Co. best known for?",
        "content" : [
            "Potato chips",
            "Fine wines",
            "Chewing gum",
            "Baby Food"
        ],
        "correct" : 3
    },
    {
        "question" : "In which of these household appliances would you find a lint screen?",
        "content" : [
            "Dishwasher",
            "Microwave oven",
            "Clothes dryer",
            "Trash compactor"
        ],
        "correct" : 2
    },
    {
        "question" : "What are the three primary colors?",
        "content" : [
            "Red, green, blue",
            "Magenta, pink, cyan",
            "Yellow, salmon, brown",
            "White, grey, black"
        ],
        "correct" : 0
    },
    {
        "question" : "What are the three primary colors?",
        "content" : [
            "Bla, Bla",
            "Magenta, Magenta",
            "salmon, salmon, salmon",
            "White, grey, black"
        ],
        "correct" : [0, 1, 2]
    }
]
}